bux4real.com 2011-03-10

# Bux4Real

Bux4Real is highly committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The purpose of this policy page is to inform you of the information Bux4Real may gather about you when you use the site or services, and how

that information may be used. Please note this privacy policy only applies to Bux4Real. Other websites we link to are not governed by this privacy policy. This policy makes known the practices for Bux4Real

hereafter referenced as Bux4Real, “us”, “we” or “the Site”.

Please review this policy adequately. By using the Site or it’s services, you agree to the terms of these policies.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**  
We collect personally identifiable information only when you knowingly submit that information to us. If you do not wish to provide this information, you may still use the Site but may not be able to access any services that require

such information. Bux4Real will never sell, give away or rent your personal information. Bux4Real keeps statistical records as with most websites. These logs contain a record of URL’s visited through the

service. These logs are not personally viewed or revealed to any organization.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**  
Keeping our user’s personally identifiable information secure and protected is our highest priority and we take all precautions possible to keep data secure. However due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee the

security of any data transmission or information you send to us or through us by using our services, and you agree to use our site or services at your own risk.

**DISCLOSURE**  
All use of our site is confidential. We never disclose user information unless in good faith where law requires it, or when disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be using our

service in a malicious way, or disturbing Bux4Real’s property.

In the event of a donation or other transfer of some or all of Bux4Real, you agree that we can accordingly provide the information that has been provided to us. However, the donating party cannot use any personal

information you have provided in a way that is incoherent with this Privacy Policy without your consent.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION USAGE**  
Bux4Real may provide aggregate information about our Users with sponsors and other third parties. We also use this information in a non-personally identifiable way. This information is used to modify our content and

advertising and to further tailor the Site or services.  
**  
USE OF COOKIES**  
Bux4Real may require cookies to be enabled to use the Bux4Real site or services. While using our services, you may receive cookies from other websites, such as organizations or sponsors.

Bux4Real does not control these cookies or use this data.

**PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use any personal information you may submit to us in a way that is incoherent with this policy.
